sarkarinaukriupdates.com 2017-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Sarkari Naukri Updates

**Privacy Policy for[sarkari naukri](http://www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com/) updates**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@sarkarinaukriupdates.com

At www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Sarkari naukri updates does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or  
other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our **sarkari naukri blog.  **Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com and other sites on the  
Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>[ ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad  
networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/ or to personalise the advertising content that you see.

www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You  
should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad  
servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for  
instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.sarkarinaukriupdates.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and  
we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web  
sites.

If  
you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with  
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective  
websites.
